



+55 48 99100-6117

FRONTEND DEVELOPER





oscaryopan.netlify.app



# **ABOUT ME**

I have been working in another area for the last 11 years, but that was never my dream and that was an a frustation for me. Since I discover the developing, I feel mysel realized, in many times during my studies and pratices, feel not working or studing, I'm having fun! And now I'm looking for an opportunity to enter this wonderful area, programming.

# **SKILLS**

**HTML** 

CSS

JavaScript

React JS

Git / Github



## **EXPERIENCES**

#### Copy Line LTDA 2017 - 2024

PRINTER TECHNICIAN

Maintenance of Copy Machines and Printers of different brands.

Konica Minolta Business Solutions BR 2013 - 2017 PRINTER TECHNICIAN

Konica Minolta Specialist Copier and Printer Maintenance.

#### Dominy Climatização 2012 - 2013

TECHNICIAN SUPPORT

Corrective maintenance and installation of air conditioning, of various brands and models.

### Maschall Copiadoras LTDA 2009 - 2012

PRINTER TECHNICIAN

Maintenance of Copy Machines and Printers of different brands.

## **EDUCATION**

2023 - In Progress

**UDEMY** 

Vocational course Learning JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJS, NextJS, Styled-Components, Testing with Jest, Storybook, Strapi

JavaScript / React JS etc. Teacher: Luiz Otávio Miranda.

2022

Curso em Video

HTML / CSS

Vocational course Basic to advanced HTML5 and CSS3 course, with an introduction to JavaScript. Teacher: Gustavo Guanabara.

2019 **IFSC** 

**PUBLIC MANAGEMENT** 

Undegraduate degree in Public Management at the Federal Institute of Santa Catarina (IFSC).

2002 CFFFT-SC

**High School d Degree** 

High School degree at the Centro Federal de Educação tecnológica do Estado de Santa Catarina, with Electrotechnical Specialization.